Anywhere you are, let me stretch my hand to the screen.
I want you to believe - anywhere you are, right now, it's about to happen.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
The right hand of God is power.
Right now place your hand.
Anywhere - place it.
Chain of fibroid - be disconnected!
Chain of fibroid,
low sperm count,
worm,
tube blockage,
in the name of Jesus Christ!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Open your mouth.
SCOAN Mass Prayer
Watch the screen and see what is happening.
More people are vomitting out.
Just continue to watch the screen and see what is happening live and direct in our midst.
SCOAN Mass Prayer
Watch the screen.
That is another one right there.
You can see what is coming out of her body.
Watch the screen, see what is coming out!
You have three fibroids and two have come out.
It remains one and it will come out right now.
Two are out already, one is to go.
SCOAN Mass Prayer
Watch the screen.
Something has fallen into my pants, as the man of God has said.
Thank you, I am going to the toilet.
Watch the screen.
This is happening right now, right here.
The woman vomitted what has been the tube blockage in her life.
Watch your screen right now.
That is the one that dropped in her pants.
Watch your screen.
It has come out already, all the fibroids in her system.
Open your eyes and watch.
Stretch your hand and say, "Lord, manifest Yourself in my life". Prayer.
SCOAN Mass Prayer
Low sperm count,
tube blockage,
worm,
in the name of Jesus Christ.
Prayer.
Watch your screen.
That is fibroid.
There is a woman passing out her fibroid right there.
SCOAN Mass Prayer
Place your hand.
Keep watching your screen.
SCOAN Mass Prayer
Here I am with all I have
I raise my hands to worship You
I wanna say thank You
O thank You
For everything for who You are
You cover me and touch my heart
I wanna say thank You
O thank You
Give thanks to God.
Begin to give thanks to God and share your testimony with your neighbour.
If you must receive, you must learn to plant.
I told you some weeks ago how to start this.
Get a carton and make a hole and cello tape it round.
Every day should be your offering.
We are not saying you should bring it to the church.
Every day.
Do not depend on your salary.
God does not know anything about your salary.
He promised to bless you every day.
If you want to be receiving blessing, mercy and favour,
every day, have this carton. Put it inside your bedroom.
As you go out and come in, put something inside this carton -
something your life depends on.
Towards the end of the week, anytime you are free,
take the money; don't count the money. Put it inside an envelope.
Take it to the fatherless, widows, physically challenged.
Everything about you is supposed to be new.
Your destiny needs to be reshaped.
Giving offers us an opportunity of reshaping our destiny.
Tell your neighbour, "Giving offers us an opportunity of reshaping our destiny".
When we say 'giving',
what you give does not matter, but the way and manner you give it.
Whatever you want to give must be given cheerfully.
Cheerfully.
Before you can give something cheerfully, that thing must be something
your life depends on - something you need, not something you don't need.
It's not all the time you give what you don't need.
Many times, you should give what you need also.
Something you want, you should be able to give it.
The problem we are facing is not too far.
Not that you don't give but you give what you don't need.
You should be able to give two days in a week out of seven days -
something you need.
Ah, I need this thing. I need it.
Open your warehouse, your garage. Take a new tyre, not a used tyre.
Can you imagine how many people you have killed in the past
through your offering; through your unworthy offering.
You keep giving tyres you don't need - used tyres - and
these people you're giving - they cherish it.
They would now use it for a vehicle that is going for a long distance.
Before they know it, the tyre bursts, and thousands die.
Can you imagine what your unworthy offering has done?
Out of seven days in a week, you must be able to give two days -
something your life depends on - something you need.
If not, your offering is unworthy.
I want you to make this decision.
Let me see your hand up.
Right now, decision!
Stretch your hand.
Stretch it forward.
As you stretch your hand, you are ready to make a decision.
Don't wait till you have a box. Get a carton.
You and your husband, put the money together.
You housewife, you don't have a job or husband, whatever little you are doing.
The best time to give is when you don't have.
When you begin to have so much, you cannot give what your life depends on.
But when you have little, if you can give out of that little,
wow!
Tell your neighbour, "The best time to give is when you don't have".
So thank you.
Hallelujah!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 14/07/2018 + Mel